{"question":"5 + 0 = ?", "answer":"5", "Explanation": "because it is"}
{"question":"10 + 10 = ?", "answer":"20", "Explanation": "because it is"}
{"question":"2 + 1 = ?", "answer":"3", "Explanation": "because it is"}
{"question":"9 + 7 = ?", "answer":"16", "Explanation": "because it is"}
{"question":"7 + 8 = ?", "answer":"15", "Explanation": "because it is"}
{"question":"5 + 0 = ?", "answer":"5", "Explanation": "because it is"}
{"question":"10 + 10 = ?", "answer":"20", "Explanation": "because it is"}
{"question":"2 + 1 = ?", "answer":"3", "Explanation": "because it is"}
{"question":"9 + 7 = ?", "answer":"16", "Explanation": "because it is"}
{"question":"7 + 8 = ?", "answer":"15", "Explanation": "because it is"}
{"question":"7 + 8 = ?", "answer":"15", "Explanation": "because it is"}